<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/">
  <channel>
    <title>Posts on Asier&#39;s Webpage</title>
    <link>https://123jimenez99.github.io/posts.html</link>
    <description>Recent content in Posts on Asier&#39;s Webpage</description>
    <image>
      <title>Asier&#39;s Webpage</title>
      <url>https://123jimenez99.github.io/%3Clink%20or%20path%20of%20image%20for%20opengraph,%20twitter-cards%3E</url>
      <link>https://123jimenez99.github.io/%3Clink%20or%20path%20of%20image%20for%20opengraph,%20twitter-cards%3E</link>
    </image>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Sun, 11 Jun 2023 16:20:03 +0200</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="https://123jimenez99.github.io/posts/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    <item>
      <title>Multiply your Archive Team Warriors with Docker and some little scripting</title>
      <link>https://123jimenez99.github.io/posts/multiply_archive_team_warrior_instances_with_docker.html</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 11 Jun 2023 16:20:03 +0200</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://123jimenez99.github.io/posts/multiply_archive_team_warrior_instances_with_docker.html</guid>
      <description>The Archive Team plays a crucial role in preserving online content, and its significance becomes even more pronounced when considering platforms like Reddit, which may be prone to vanishing due to their very questionable practices. Without further ado let&amp;rsquo;s explain how this works.
The warrior runs on your computer and connects to the Archive Team server. It receives instructions on which websites to archive and contributes to the archiving process. Whenever a new archiving project is launched, the server assigns specific tasks to each Warrior.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>How could modern compilers unleash the potential of the CELL processor?</title>
      <link>https://123jimenez99.github.io/posts/what_if_cell_modern_compiler.html</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 06 Jun 2023 22:45:34 +0200</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://123jimenez99.github.io/posts/what_if_cell_modern_compiler.html</guid>
      <description>Have you ever wondered what the fate of the Cell processor would have been like if the software designed for it could have been coded making use of the compilers we have today? In this article, I will explain the complications and limitations of the Cell processor, as well as how a modern compiler can drastically help optimize the code for it.
Before we proceed, let&amp;rsquo;s quickly take a look at the design of the Cell processor: The Cell processor consists of a scalar dual-threaded PowerPC core (PPE) and eight vector coprocessors (SPE) that communicate via an internal bus (EIB).</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>A curated list of unbiased tech content creators</title>
      <link>https://123jimenez99.github.io/posts/yt_recomended.html</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 02 Mar 2023 12:10:01 +0200</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://123jimenez99.github.io/posts/yt_recomended.html</guid>
      <description>Over the years, I’ve gathered a small list of exceptional content creators who are truly worth watching. Most of these focus on technology and anyone is involved in shilling or promoting any products. Whether you’re interested in Raspberry Pis, retro computing, code optimization, hacking, or exploring the mechanics of video games pushed to their limits, these channels offer unique and engaging content that will surely captivate your interest.
More Bits inside by René Rebe René Rebe, the creator of the T2 distro with support for multiple architectures, deserves recognition for his consistent contributions to the community.</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>
